

# 0

Veldbrugstraat 63 9060 Zelzate



+32470807730



<u>Stef.claeyssens@telenet.</u> <u>be</u>

Stef.claeyssens@student.hogent.be



www.linkedin.com/in/st ef-claeyssens-8a69051a2

## Stef Claeyssens - CV

#### **Foreword**

#### I am Stef Claeyssens,

22 years old, final year Applied Computer Science student at University College Ghent and aspiring Full Stack Developer with a great love for Front-end development in web and mobile environments. With my passion for "making" (from crafts to websites), I would describe myself as very creative and persevering, with a keen eye for detail and a strive for perfection. In my spare time I am an active leader and volunteer within the Scouts and Guides Flanders - Vuurtorengroep where, in my now 16 years, I have learned to work in a group with both young and old, to be flexible and communicative and have taken on a leadership role. With my eagerness to work and learn, I do not shy away from large projects and challenges.

#### Personalia

- Name: Claeyssens Stef - Date of birth: 02/03/1999

- Place of residence: Veldbrugstraat 63, 9060 Zelzate - National Registration number: 99.03.02-357.34

- Cell number: +32470807730

- E-mailaddress: <a href="mailed:stef.claeyssens@telenet.be">stef.claeyssens@telenet.be</a>, stef.claeyssens@student.hogent.be

- Drivers license: type B

#### **Work experience**

2015-present

Magazijnier • DSV Logistics Gent

2021-present

Bandwerk • Adient Belgium

#### **Education**

Professional Bachelor in Applied Computer Science, Ghent University College

Specialization in Mobile Application and Enterprise Web Development

2017-present

Diploma in Secondary Education, Science Mathematics (6h), Sint-Laurensscholen Zelzate

2013-2017



#### **Skills**

- Java
- Javascript
- Typescript (Angular)
- C# (.NET)
- HTML, (S)CSS
- SQL
  - Database programming in SQL Server
- UML
  - > Design using design patterns
- Kotlin (Android)
- Spring Boot
- Swift (iOS) (trainee)

#### Realisations

- Mastermind desktop game (Java)
- Classroom organizer tool (Java, .NET, SQL Server Database)
- Scouting organizer tool (backend: .NET, frontend: Angular, SQL Server Database)
- Hiking app + website (backend: .NET, frontend: Angular, mobile: Kotlin – Android, SQL Server Database)
  - Commissioned by ©Damiaanactie

## **Leadership**

## **Active leader and volunteer**

within Scouts and Guides Flanders, Vuurtorengroep Zelzate

### **Ex-Head Leader**

within Scouts and Guides Flanders, Vuurtorengroep Zelzate

#### Co-Organiser Katse Feesten, 5-day festival

Made possible by Scouts and Guides Flanders, Vuurtorengroep Zelzate

#### **Vice Chairman Youth Council**

Within local city council of Zelzate

## Language knowledge

Dutch

Native

**English** 

Very fluent and understanding

French

Fluent and understanding

German

**Notions** 





